AntonyWuth

contact

100 Eucumbene Dr Duffy, ACT, 2611 Australia

+61 (0) 414 254 157 +61 (02) 6287 4506

ajw@pobox.com

Linux Solaris

IT administration

Oracle Database
Data Communications
TCP/IP Networking
ICT Metric's
Internet Services
DNS
HTTP
ICT Security

ICT Design

SOE Security Gateway environments Network Web Applications

ICT Audit

Security
Firewall review
Networks
Log management and
review

Languages

Perl Java PHP VGL

IT Management

Continous Intergration / Dev Systems Monitoring Network Monitoring

personal history

I worked under contract as a theatrical technician as well as running a private help desk before becoming a contract programmer in February 1998. I have supported and developed for life critical systems such as the Sample Manager Laboratory Management product at the Australian Water Quality Center (AWQC). I am proficient in a number of different programming languages, with the skills to rapidly learn new languages as required. I am experienced in the installation and maintenance of Oracle systems running under AIX, Solaris, Windows and Linux. I have considerable experience in network installations specialising in TCP/IP. I have been involved in the specification and roll out of secured public access systems. I have also worked with both small business and large enterprises to implement reliable, secured and cost effective networks.

Staff Management

Throughout my career I have been required to manage staff, a role I am comfortable in filling. Whilst at the Department of the Environment I was initially responsible for managing a small development team, and then progressing to a section of sixteen IT professionals with a variety of skills. I enjoy the interaction that comes with a management role and look forward to continuing this aspect of my career.

B

LAH BLAH BLAH

employment

employment

2013-Now Australian Government, Department of the Environment can-

berra, Australia

Director Platform Services Section Duties:

- Lead and manage a diverse team of ICT professionals.
- Manage multi-million dollar operational and project budgets
- Project management of both internal and externally delivered systems.
- provide advice, participate and manage ICT procurement activities including large tender processes. Including large whole of government activities.
- Assist in new strategic initiatives both directly and via participation in steering committees and working groups.
- Manage external providers and consultants.
- Implement and manage mixed Linux and Windows servers.
- Participate in key audit processes including implementation of recommendations.
- Deliver key infrastructure projects:
 - Migration to new Secured intranet Gateway
 - Design and implementation of new MAN network design
 - Implemenation of system configuration management system (pupept)
 - Oracle Database and infrastructure upgrades

2008-2013 Australian Government, Department of Sustainability, Environment, Water, Population and Communities Canberra, Australia Director Environmental and Business Information Systems Section

Duties:

- Lead and manage a diverse team of ICT professionals.
- Manage multi-million dollar operational and project budgets
- Project management of both internal and externally delivered systems.
- Assist in new strategic initiatives both directly and via participation in steering committees.
- Manage external providers and consultants.
- Implement and manage mixed Linux and Windows

2004-2008 Australian Government, Department of Environment and Heritage Canberra, Australia

Database and Internet Officer

Duties:

- Develop, implement and manage Internet applications.
- Implement and manage mixed Unix (Solaris) and Windows servers.
- Provide support for web based applications to both internal and external clients
- Manage relationships with external providers and consultants.
- Manage APS level staff.
- Train and assist clients to effectively utilise information systems.

2002-2004 Cape3

Canberra, Australia

Senior Analyst - Web Programmer

Duties:

- Design of back-end databases, including integration with legacy systems.
- Implementations of designs in:
 - ColdFusion
 - Perl
 - HTML
 - PHP
- Assisting graphics designers to realise their vision.
- Design and specification of systems and network upgrades.
- Preparation of tender responses

1998-2002 Australian Water Quality Centre

Boliver, South Australia

Page 3 of 5

Analyst / Programmer

Duties:

- Power Builder development
- Development of database reporting software
- Migration and cleansing of data from legacy systems
- Interfacing financial and laboratory systems
- Design and implementation of work scheduling systems
- Support for Sample Manager
- Maintenance and improvement of Laboratory Information systems
- VGL Programming

awards

2009 Secretary's Award Department of the Environment, Water, Heritage and the Arts

Awarded for sustained contribution towards realising the

Department's outcomes

2007 Division head's Award Corporate Stratigies Division, Department of the Environment

Awarded for excellent management of the Department's mid-range database, infrastructure and web information

systems

2007 Division head's Award Corporate Stratigies Division, Department of the Environment

Awarded for excellentsupport to the Department's web in-

formation systems

communication skills

2013 Oral Presentation

Splunk live

Presented the Department's implementation of splunk as a security and log management system.

education

2012	Splunk, search administration, installation		
2011	Project Management Best Practice	Dept. of Environment and Heritage	
2004-presen	004-presentOracle Database Administration and feature updatesoracle Corperation		
1999	Oracle Database Administration	Oracle Corperation, Canberra	
1999	Sample Manager Administrtion	LabSystems Australia, Adelaide	
1998	Sample Manager Advanced VGL Programmers, Sydney	gramming LabSystems	
1997	Diploma Diploma of Business Programming Computer Power Training Institute, Canberra C, COBOL, Visual Basic, SQL, business applications, operating systems and network operating systems		
1993	Year 12 Certificate	St Edmunds College, Canberra	

interests

professional: ICT & physical security, solution design, systems automation, process quality improvment personal: cycling, fish-keeping, home-automation, electronics, embedded programming, wood working.